伙计们 你们绝对想不到刚刚出什么事了
You guys. You guys will not believe what just happened.
我来这的路上
On my way here,
一辆出租车开上了路边 压住了一个老太太
a taxi jumped the curb and it pinned this old lady,
然后我打了鸡血一样的冲了过去
and I-I just went into this, like, crazy adrenaline mode
我把那个老太救了出来
and I somehow lifted it off her.
噢 老天 泰德 你的手腕
Oh, my God, Ted, your wrist.
哦 是 我觉得就是有点浮肿
Oh, yeah, I guess it's a little swollen.
应该是抬那出租车的时候弄伤了
I must've strained it lifting.
我觉得我亲爱的朋友莉莉说的是
I believe our dear friend Lily was referring
你的另外一个手腕
to your other wrist.
戴着男士避孕环的那个
The one wearing the male birth control.
我认为那是一个
I was gonna go with
贞操手镯
"Chastity bracelet."
天啊 我还能再多爱你一点吗
God, is it possible to love you more?
有没有搞错啊
Really? Really?
我刚刚救了一条人命 你们两个就只注意这个
I just saved someone's life, and you guys are focusing on this?
对 伙计们 别管他
Yeah, you know what, guys? Leave him alone.
他是个英雄
All right, he's a hero.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不觉得你的超能力来自于
Do you think that your super strength came from
女超人的魔法护腕吗
wearing Wonder Woman's magic wrist cuff?
对 我要让你们知道因为这个护腕
Yeah, I'll have you know that because of this cuff,
今天佳人有约
I have a date.
靠护手霜和约炮神器吗
With some hand lotion and the Internet?
我确实还能再多爱你一点
It is possible to love you more!
她是真实存在的
She exists.
她就在外面
And she's right outside.
很好 带她进来
Great. Bring her in.
不觉得吗 今日天气甚好
You know what? It's so nice out.
不如我们出去散散步吧
Why don't... why don't we just all go for a walk.
外面瓢泼大雨 泰德 我觉得很明显
It's pouring rain, Ted. I think it's pretty obvious
她是太胖了进不来
she can't fit through the door. Mm.
她是个极好的 运动型的女人
She is a gorgeous, athletic woman.
运动型 其实就是平胸
"Athletic"? Sideburns, no cans.
她超火辣的
She is hot.
那她为啥就不能进来呢 泰德
So why can't she come in, Ted?
她可以进来
She can come in.
六个半月以后
In six and a half months.
等一下 你是说她
Wait. Are you saying she's...
20岁
Twenty.
半
And a half.
还没到
Almost.
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季 第十四集
翻译:@Mr_Gao703 @CIA_Kevin @神RoyShiCheng
@Big-Fudge @苏赛崽
校对:@苏赛崽 @神RoyShiCheng
统筹+后期:@苏赛崽 @神RoyShiCheng
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献
等等 伙计们
Ah-ah! Hold up, guys.
她得走了 一个快闪突然出现在了威廉斯堡
She had to bounce. Um, a flash mob broke out in front
的一个棒子墨西哥餐车的前面
of a line of Korean-Mexican food trucks in Williamsburg.
唯一能让她
The only thing
快速超过20岁的方法
that would make her more of a 20-year-old
冷笑话一则 怎样快速到21岁 答 滑过去
是一种交通工具
is an ironic form
-这冷爆了  -耶
-of transportation. -Yeah.
她是滑轮滑过去的
She's roller skating there.
我不知道哪一个更可悲了
I don't know which is more pathetic--
是你跟一个20岁的人约会
that you're going out with a 20-year-old
还是你为了跟她约会买了一个皮革护腕
or that you bought a leather cuff to get a date with her.
我才不是买这个
I didn't buy this
就是为了约会
to get a date.
我只是偶然出去
I just happened to be out
赶上了某个周六下午的
catching up on some Saturday afternoon
皮革护腕的展销会
leather cuff shopping, Oh.
然后她碰巧就在那卖护腕
and she just happened to be a leather cuff saleswoman.
天啊 我很高兴我不在外面追女人了
God, I am so glad I am done chasing bimbos.
我现在订婚了 那些追女人的日子
Now that I'm engaged, that whole part of my life
真是悲哀又空虚
just seems sad and empty.
不是我说的难听
I don't want this to sound
泰德 你让我恶心
too harsh, Ted, but you disgust me.
一个月前你的床头柜上还有台自动润滑油售货机
Until a month ago, your headboard had a lube dispenser.
呃 对
Uh, yeah.
-我们不再那样了 好吧  -对
-We got rid of that, okay? -Yeah.
总之 说到订婚
Anyway, speaking of engaged,
看看这个改过尺寸拿回来的东西
check out what got back from being resized.
哦 天啊 看看这钻石有多大
Oh, my God. Look at the size of that rock.
巴尼 你没有
Barney, you don't
用那个"捉奸之钻"
start with the I-got-caught-cheating diamond.
你成熟了
You give yourself room to grow.
这是个传家宝
It's a family heirloom.
对 圣诞节时
Yeah, I got a few dirty looks
我被巴尼同父异母的妹妹小小的鄙视了一下
from Barney's half-sister over Christmas,
所以我必须坐下来很尊重的跟她解释
so I had to sit her down and explain very respectfully...
让她滚犊子了
that she can suck it.
好吧
Okay.
我得走了
I got to bounce.
别再那么说了
Stop saying that.
这个迪拜来的DJ
This DJ from Dubai is spinning
在布什维克的一个废弃的码头打转
at an abandoned loading dock in Bushwick.
我怕我穿的太少了
I'm worried I don't have enough layers.
如果我朋友们
So what if my friends
觉得这是注定的呢
thought it was doomed?
我还年轻 我知道那晚跟一个
I was still young, and I knew that a night of partying
比我小十几岁的女孩参加聚会
with a girl over a decade younger than me
会是完全的
would be a total...
灾难 她就像是完全不同的物种
...disaster. She's like an entirely different species.
我确实是穿的太少了
And I definitely didn't have enough layers.
她说的话有一半我都听不懂
I didn't understand half the words she was saying.
对我来说 那听起来就像是流行的疯狂填词
To me, it all sounded like hipster Mad Libs.
你看手机了没
Didn't you check your phone?
o
I just "Means of contacting" You
此乃90后美少女火星文
鲭ㄋ
on "Currently hot social networking site."
m^l
The show's been moved
搬KH
to "New York neighborhood
oi
you've never heard of."
哦 哇 我手机上还有表呢
Oh. Wow, my phone has a clock.
而且他们赖以生存的饮食上一堆毫无意义的奇怪组合
And they subsist on a diet of pointlessly weird combinations.
哦
Ooh.
嘿 你想和我一起吃一个拌菜味
Hey, do you want to split a kimchi cupcake
上面撒上培根霜的蛋糕吗
with bacon frosting?
这里做的最好吃了
They are the best here.
哦 好啊 那种食物和我这个
Uh, yeah. Yeah, that'll go great with my
黄瓜小辣椒鸡蛋汁很搭
cucumber jalape?o egg cream.
赶紧都喝了 走吧 走吧
Chug it! Come on. Come on.
-我们该走了  -好吧
-We got to get going. -Right. Okay.
晚些时候 一个坐落在在中国城的
Then later, at a club in Chinatown
不知道在什么地方的下水井盖下面的俱乐部里
somehow located beneath a manhole cover,
事情就变得很诡异了
it got weird.
天 我真的好喜欢你
God, I just love those
眉毛里那些灰色的小毛毛
tiny gray hairs in your eyebrows.
老人真的好性感
Old men are so sexy.
好吧 是这样的
All right, to be fair,
一些灰色的眉毛是鸡蛋汁干了造成的
some of those gray hairs were dried egg cream.
原因是 当你滑旱冰滑到吐的时候
Turns out, when you projectile vomit on skates,
你会直接摔在你吐的那一摊东西上
you roll right into the spray.
等等 她觉得你多大啊
Wait, how old does she think you are?
你参加过越南战争吗
So, were you in Vietnam?
先别叫 我还没说完呢
Hold that groan.
越共漫山遍野
Charlie was everywhere.
她超辣的 她就喜欢老人
She's hot! She likes old guys!
别来批评我
Don't judge me!
然后我们走进舞厅
Anyway, when we got out on the dance floor, th...
我发誓 那些二十岁的小年轻看起来都像...
I swear, this is what all the 20-year-olds looked like...
列兵 感谢您为国效力 国家和人民是不会忘记你的
I want to thank you for your service to this nation, Private.
是上校好不
Colonel.
我该把这事了结了
I got to end this.
是啊 真的 泰德
Yeah, seriously, Ted.
为了一夜春宵假装成别人
Pretending to be someone else just to get laid?
可真丢人
That's... embarrassing.
参见殿下
Your Highness!
我们快走吧
Let's go.
哦 马修 把那东西摘下来
Ew. Marshall, take that off.
怎么啦 我觉得这东西很酷啊
What? I think it looks kind of cool.
很酷
Cool?
你看起来就像很怂的乐队里的那些混混
You look like one of those jerks who's in some lame band
骑摩托不戴头盔子 钱包上拴个小链子
and rides a motorcycle without a helmet and has a wallet chain
纹身纹了满脖子 没事儿吸个小毒子
and neck tattoos and a drug problem.
不是...一个大的...就是...
Not a... A big one, just, uh...
在路边跟他开个价 磨叽一会儿
enough that he deals a little bit on the side, and...
然后他永远都不会真诚对待女人的那种
he can never... ever be true to one woman.
赶紧吃掉那个切糕 干我吧
Finish that damn pickle and do me!
好吧 你们知道我的早晨一般都怎么过吗
Okay, you guys know how my mornings usually go.
我们为啥要知道
Why would we care how...
一般情况下都是这样度过的
Usually it's like this.
你先来
After you.
哦 谢谢
Aw, thank you.
免费的 罗宾
On the house, Robin!
面包圈给你免费滴
Take this bagel on the house
报纸送你免费滴
Have a paper on the house
这栋房子都免费送你
I'd give you a house on the house
如果我真的可以
If I could
你就是如此美丽
You're so beautiful
每天都该免费拿东西
Everything in life should be free
做人做到我这份上是多惬意
It's so wonderful to be me!
哇哦
Wow.
是不是每天早上都有小蓝鸟帮你穿衣服呢
Do little bluebirds help you get dressed in the morning, too?
她只不过是夸张一点来
She's exaggerating
举个例子而已
To make a point!
但是今天就不一样了
But today was different.
一共3块7毛5
That'll be $3.75.
但我昨天并没交钱啊
But I didn't have to pay yesterday.
好的 那就7块5
Okay. $7.50.
-哦 我的小可怜啊  -都是因为戒指 罗宾
-Oh, honey-sweetie-baby. -It's the ring, Robin.
戒指是有能量的
The ring has power.
当一个女人戴上订婚戒指
When a woman puts on an engagement ring,
它就像指环王里面的比尔博・巴金斯
it's like when Bilbo Baggins wears the One Ring
戴着至尊魔戒一样
in The Hobbit.
好吧 你能重新说一遍 但是稍微不那么像死宅吗
Okay, can you say that again but not in nerd?
好的 戒指就像斗篷
Sure. Uh, the ring is like the cloak
和哈利波特穿着到处乱跑的那件斗篷效果一样
that Harry Potter wears to sneak around Hogwarts.
好吧 我也不说处男语
Yeah, I don't speak virgin either.
那戒指 让你隐形
The ring-- it makes you invisible.
你不是宝贝
You're not precious.
模仿魔戒说的 "you are my precious"
哦 太好了 你还没睡
Oh, good, you're awake.
听着 泰德
Look, Ted,
有些事情我们要谈一谈
there's something we have to talk about.
朋友之间的尺度 侵犯隐私
Boundaries? Invasion of privacy?
剥夺你的钥匙权
Losing your key privileges?
是关于那个20岁的女孩的 泰德
It's about the 20-year-old, Ted.
你必须得把她上了
You have to bang her.
为了我
For me!
为什么你想让我和一个20多岁的女孩勾搭在一起
Why do you want me to hook up with this 20-year-old?
我以为这么做让你恶心了
I thought I disgusted you.
是啊 那全都是装的
Yeah, that was all an act.
你看 那个 我爱罗宾
Look, look, look, I love Robin
她是我唯一想跟着一起生活的女人
and she's the only girl I want to be with.
但我的身体在四年内 经历的各种一夜情已让我中毒已深
But my body is detoxing after years of one-night stands.
他们又没为这种事情像戒烟戒酒一样
They don't make
弄个口香糖或者贴个贴什么的
gum or a patch for this, Ted.
但是 嘿 又一个金点子哦
But, hey, billion-dollar idea alert.
对 就写这里了
Oh, yeah here here.
好吧 我还是买本新的梦境日志好了
That's okay. I'll just buy a new dream journal.
你现在想找什么
What-what-what are you looking for?
你的电话
Your phone.
里面一定有她的图片什么的
There's got to be some pictures of her in here.
我去 不是吧
Damn it. No.
这些都毫无价值啊
Those are all worthless.
我需要些一夜情的素材啊 泰德亲
I need some one-night-stand material, Ted.
啊 这张是你麻麻的照片 你好啊 维吉尼亚
Oh. Oh. Here's your mom. Hello, Virginia.
呃 我妈可不是一夜情的素材
Um, my mother is not one-night-stand material.
对 你说的没错 那不是夜里 而且咱们也没有"情"
Yeah, you're right. It wasn't night and we weren't standing.
哈哈
Hey-oh!
那不可能发生过
That didn't happen.
没错 是没发生过
You're right. It didn't.
你刚刚眨眼了
You just winked.
才没有呢
No, I didn't.
你又来了
You just did it again!
听好了 总之 我需要你
Look, bottom line: I need you
代替我把那妹子睡了
to proxy bang this girl for me.
做我的替身
Be my stand-in
用你的身体压之
and put your gland in.
对了 这句话印在帽子上感觉不错
Hey, wow, that'd be good on a hat.
巴尼
Barney,
她只是看中我这朵优雅的风中残烛罢了
she's just using me for my gracefully aging body.
你现在知道为了面子得挑点靠谱的人选啦
You're picking now to get some self-respect?
你之前在把一个盲妹子的时候 还把自己装成肖恩?康纳利
You once banged a blind girl by pretending to be Sean Connery.
第一代詹姆斯?邦德
那是你好伐
That was you.
是的 那是我平生最愉悦的任务
Yeah, that conquest was most enjoyable.
模仿邦德说话
抱歉 要我拿下那妹子
I'm sorry. T-To hook up with a girl,
我得找到共鸣 哪怕只有一点也行啊
I have to connect with her at least a little.
那就共鸣去啊
Then find a connection.
搞简单点
Just go simple.
别扯那些怪怪的诗词建筑
Nothing about weird poets or buildings
或者你曾经发给我的那些题为
or any of those stupid articles you've ever e-mailed me
题为 心灵鸡汤 的二逼小文章
with the subject line "Food for thought."
求你了 泰德
Please, Ted.
我要嘛
I need this.
败给你了
Fine. You win.
我这就去搞定一个二十岁辣妹
I'll bang a hot 20-year-old.
但我不会觉得愉悦
But I'm not gonna enjoy...
别欺骗自己了
Oh, who am I kidding?
那肯定爽爆了好吧
It's gonna be awesome.
现在 关上灯 然后走你
Now, turn off the lights and go.
留个小灯
Not all the way!
哈 三瓶...
Hello. Yeah, three...
以往纽约是全世界最友好
Okay, normally New York is the friendliest,
最便宜的城市了有木有
most affordable city in the world.
现在这儿就跟旧金山一样又粗鲁又花钱
Now it's as rude and expensive as San Francisco.
伙计们
Guys?
嗯 这就是你订婚了以后的生活状态
Oh, hey, that's life once you're engaged.
告诉她 宝贝儿 让她心碎去吧
Oh, tell her, baby. Make it hurt.
咱们卡座见
I'll be at the booth.
我的小内内现在穿没穿 不一定
My panties may or may not be on
不过等到了卡座
when you get there.
那就一定脱掉了
They won't be!
你们两个发什么神经啊
Okay, what is going on with you guys?
是这腕带
It's the cuff.
总之把自己描绘成一个失意的音乐家
It turns out that picturing me as a loser musician
再加上对维柯丁上瘾并有一台小用来
with a Vicodin addiction and a beat-up van
偷铜线的小破车能让莉莉性致盎然
I use to steal copper wire really turns Lily's crank.
谁知道呢
Who knew?
哇 你的手腕怎么了
Whoa, what-what happened to your wrist?
呃 我对它过敏
Oh. It's an allergic reaction.
那快点摘下来啊
So take it off.
罗宾 你若为人父母
Robin, once you have a child,
任何能够增加哪怕一点点上床概率的神器
anything that gets you even remotely close
都值得你去忍受一些充满脓水的脓包
to the possibility of sex is worth a few pus-filled blisters.
欢愉会压过苦楚的
Better the sores weep than I.
喂 等会儿 这贱货才到的这儿
Hey, hold on. That slut just got here.
她已经拿到啤酒了
How'd she get beer already?
你看到她手指头上有戒指没
Do you see a ring on that finger?
等会儿 脑子有点乱
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你说的那些被无视什么的
Are you saying that this invisibility thing
意味着我连啤酒都拿不到
means I might not be able to get beer?
我才刚刚适应要自己付钱买咖啡
I was just getting used to the idea of having to pay for coffee
买面包圈交房租的事情
and bagels and rent.
-连房租都  -但我连啤酒都喝不到
-Rent?  -But not being able to get a beer?
叔可忍 姐不能忍
Unacceptable.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
辣妹求插队
Hot girl coming through.
三瓶啤酒 谢了
Three beers, please.
我了个大擦的戒指
Damn it, ring!
等会你得去买一副小弹簧刀
Later you should totally go out and buy a switchblade.
妥妥的
Mm. Sure.
我不在那会儿 爹地也要会去买点尿布啦
While I'm out, maybe Daddy picks up some diapers
微辣莎莎酱什么的 毕竟我们库存不够了嘛
and a little mild salsa because we're low.
好吧 你们是对的
Well, you're right
我成六娃了
I'm invisible.
科普 六娃是中国传统动漫"福禄娃"中的隐形娃
那晚 唯一一个
That night, the only person
比罗宾还挫败的人是她的未婚夫
in worse shape than Robin was her fiance.
泰德 我绝望了
Ted, I'm desperate.
今天早些时候 我看到那腕带了
Earlier today, I saw that wrist cuff
然后向他默哀了
and I got a partial for Marshall.
你到底把没把到那个妹子啊
Did you bang that girl yet?
别报那么大希望 也别有任何想法
Don't get your hopes, or anything else, up.
我试着找与她的共鸣
I tried to connect with her,
可我说的所有话都回到
but everything just comes back
她喜欢老男人这种奇怪癖好
to her weird fetish about how old I am.
好吧 就说点简单的 她喜欢看电视吗
Well, j-just go simple-- does she like TV?
不喜欢
No.
但我愿意和你一起看《新闻60分》
But I'll watch 60 Minutes with you
想看多久 开多大声音 都行
as loud and as long as you want.
喜欢体育吗
Sports?
不喜欢
No.
我敢肯定你打沙壶球一定超性感
But I bet you look super hot playing shuffleboard,
就是 涂满厚厚的止痛药膏的样子
just... slathered in Bengay.
好吧 她爱读书吗
Well, does she like books?
不
No.
可我猜你一定爱读书
But I bet you do.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
我猜你一定有一副又大又厚实的
I bet you have a big, thick
近视老花镜
pair of bifocals.
她不是有恋父情结 而是有恋爷情结
She doesn't have daddy issues, she has granddaddy issues.
我不玩了
I'm ending it.
泰德 我求求你 永远不要停歇于 不停歇的娇体上
Ted, I beg of you, don't quit on a body that won't quit.
啊哦 这句话做成车贴一定好有爱
Ooh, ooh, that'll go sweet on a bumper sticker.
得赶紧写到日志上
That's going in the journal.
等等 你是不是把我的梦境日志偷走了
Wait, did you steal my dream journal?
没有啊 在你牙齿掉光 光着屁股站在摇荡山庄高中
No! Now, get back in there before all your teeth fall out
泰德高中母校
参加一个你从来没彩排过的戏剧之前
and you're naked in front of Shaker Heights High School
你赶紧给我滚过来
in a play you never rehearsed for.
魂淡
Bastard!
我们没有在任何一件事情上产生共鸣 都结束了
We don't connect on a single thing. It's over.
还没有
It's not...
你看 卡莉 我得跟你说
Look, Carly, I got to tell you something.
我就是 看不到未来
I just, I don't see a future here.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
你要死了吗
Are you dying?
这太性感了
Oh, that is so hot.
嘿
Hey...
那是R2-D2吗
is that R2-D2?
星战中的机器人之一
你喜欢星球大战吗
Do you like Star Wars?
我大爱星球大战
I love Star Wars.
我也是
Me, too!
我其实只看过新的三部曲
I mean, I've only seen the new ones.
那也差不多啦
Close enough.
这么说
So?
嗯哪
Yeah.
我就知道 我都能感觉到
I knew it! I could feel it.
就好像我们俩一起上了她
It's almost like we were hooking up with her together.
你也感觉到了 是吧
You felt that, right?
如果我能感觉到 我就不举了
I couldn't have performed if I did.
你还不明白么 泰德
Don't you see, Ted?
咱们俩兄弟心有灵犀
We had a bro-nnection.
好了好了 赶紧给我看看
All right, I got to know
她长什么样子 给我看看照片
what she looks like-- show me a picture.
好吧 平时呢 我不屑于自拍艳照
Well, normally, I'm above such things,
但已经有一阵子了 而且 泰迪得秀一下
but it's been a while, and, uh, Teddy's braggin'.
好吧 这就是她
Okay, here she is.
好 往上看...
Okay. Scrolling up.
哦也 那就是
Oh, yeah, those are
所谓的"干我"牌高跟鞋 正点
"Plow me" Heels. Nice.
膝盖上的淤青也挺带劲的
The knee bruise is encouraging.
继续往上 是一对20岁的波波
Working our way up to those 20-year-old ta-tas.
哦 可憎的地心引力还没有抓住你们
Oh... gravity's cruel grasp
我可爱的活泼的深造之物们
hasn't found you yet, my sweet perky miracles.
现在 让我们来一睹这浪女的真面容
Now, let's get a gander at Dirty Girl's face.
她的脸上就写着"准备被炮" 我没说错吧
Her face says, "Ready to bone," Am I right?
我再说一遍 我没说错吧
I say again, am I right?
那是我同父异母的妹妹
That's my half sister.
那你就不要翻看下一张照片了
Then you probably shouldn't scroll to the next picture.
不要
No!
那是我的妹妹 泰德
That's my sister, Ted!
呃 我并不知道啊
Well, look, I didn't know!
两年前我们谁都不知道你有个妹妹
None of us even knew you had a sister
你当时也不知道
until two years ago, including you!
这肯定是个疯狂的巧合
This is just some crazy coincidence.
纽约市有400万女人
There are four million women in the city of New York,
泰德 你非得睡了我妹妹
Ted, and you sleep with my sister?
苍天为什么要这样对我啊
Why would the universe do that to me?
我不知道
I don't know.
就好像你没有这样对待过女人一样
It's not like you've ever treated women in such a way
这肯定是大自然冥冥之中给你的报应
that would invite some sort of karmic retribution.
你上了我的妹妹
You banged my sister!
我可爱的 娇俏的 纯洁的
My sweet, little, innocent...
-身上还打孔的 -真的吗 在哪儿
-Pierced. Really? -Where?
别告诉我
Don't answer that!
现在我知道为什么我对昨晚感同身受了
Now I know why I felt everything you did to her last night.
那不是是兄弟灵犀 是兄妹灵犀
It wasn't a bro-nnection, it was a sis-nnection!
喔 我的天
Oh, my God.
泰德 你有没有
Ted... did you...
爽飞了
Big-time.
牛逼 击掌
Nice! High five!
等等 不对 不对
Wait! No! No!
回收击掌
Retraction five!
喂 是你求着我代替你去上她的
Hey, hey, you're the one who begged for a proxy bang.
说到家人这方面
And while we're on the subject of family,
我敢肯定你上了我妈 这比妹妹更可忍
I'm pretty sure you banged my mom-- mom beats sister.
我从没有上过你妈
I never banged your mom.
你又给我眨眼了
You just did the winking thing again!
不 我才没
No, I didn't.
好吧 嘿 巴尼 我问你
Fine. Hey, Barney, let me ask you something.
你今天早上 是不是感到有点酸痛
Were you, uh, feeling a little sore this morning?
特别是在
Especially...
从此绝交
Friendship over!
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
谁是你又弹吉他又骑摩托又找不到调味酱
Who's your guitar-player-biker- who-couldn't-find-mild-salsa-
但是说管他呢而且开始进入状态的坏小子
but-said-screw-it- and-went-medium bad boy?
马修 你的手
Marshall, your hand!
好吧 我觉得没那么糟糕
Okay, I'm pretty sure it wasn't that bad,
但你们马修叔叔的版本就是这样子滴
but this is how Uncle Marshall likes to tell the story.
哦 是啊 不 就是因为这个护腕
Oh, yeah, no, that's the cuff.
我有点头晕 我都感觉不到手指了
I'm woozy, and I can't flex my fingers...
而且臭鱼的味道好像更强烈了
...and the rotten fish smell is getting stronger.
但我可以用我的左手来弥补下
But I'm learning to compensate with my left.
难道这就是为什么昨晚我让你"捏捏咪咪"
Is that why last night when I asked you to honka honka me
你只做到了"捏咪"
you only honka'd me?
我以为你没注意到呢
I didn't think you noticed.
斯纳普可是嫉妒了喀拉寇整整一天
Snap's been jealous of Crackle all day.
马修给lily的lady parts起名字 snap crackle是两胸 详见S08E02
你就把护腕摘掉吧
Just take the cuff off.
不 宝贝 这样咱就不能继续做了
No, but, baby, then all the sex will stop.
马修 你不需要用护腕来秀性感
Marshall, you don't need a cuff for me to find you sexy.
你唯一需要做的
All you have to do
马修给lily的lady parts起名字 pop是除了两胸之外的那儿
原谅女字幕菌无法直言其名 详见S08E02
就是一个微笑 而且我已经准备让你坐到波普上了
is smile, and I'm ready for you to hop on Pop.
谢谢你亲爱的
Thanks, baby.
在咱去看急诊之前
Are you too woozy to do it one last time
你还能顶着头晕做一次吗
before we seek emergency medical attention?
试一次才知道哦
Only one way to find out.
不好意思兄弟 我的反应实在是太过了
I'm sorry, bro, I totally overreacted.
你才发现吗
You think?
真不敢相信你竟然送来一只死负鼠
I can't believe you're allowed to ship a dead possum.
他死了
He died?
那只负鼠可是和平谈判的橄榄枝啊
That possum was supposed to be an olive branch.
你确定他不是在装死吗
Are you sure he's not just playing dead?
他闻起来像马修的手
He smells like Marshall's hand.
等下 你原谅我了
And wait, you-you forgive me?
当然了 嘿 我这儿有两根"雪茄"
Absolutely. Hey, I got a couple "Cee-gars."
快过来
Get over here!
好了 你所谓的"雪茄"在哪
All right. So, where are those "Cee-gars"?
那玩意儿一会再亮出来
Eh, we'll break 'em out in a minute.
嘿 老巴
Hey, Barn.
泰德
Ted?
巴尼 你妹妹来这干嘛呢
Barney, what is your sister doing here?
没啥事哈 兄弟 或者该叫你
Nothing, bro. Or should I say,
妹夫
bro-in-law!
恭喜你啦
Congratulations!
你要娶我妹妹啦
You're marrying my sister!
看来你不惜一切代价呢 你个大傻帽
And you spared no expense, you big crazy!
你们知道吗 虽然我深爱巴尼
You know what? I love Barney,
但戒指这玩意儿真烦人
but this ring thing sucks.
有个猥琐男不小心蹭到了我的咪咪
Some gross guy just brushed up against my rack
他竟然道歉了
and then apologized.
而且是真心的道歉那种
And I think he really, really meant it.
哦 亲爱的 我知道被陌生人袭胸的感觉很美妙
Oh, sweetie, I know it's nice to be groped by strangers,
但是没有什么能比得上
but nothing beats the rush you get
那个特别的人眼里只有你的感觉
when that one special person looks at you.
她说的没错
It's true.
就像我坐在这儿 我的眼里只有一样东西
Like here in this bar, there's only one thing that I see,
就是我的小百合
and I see her brighter
比世间一切都明亮而清晰
and more clearly than anything else in this world.
你知道那是什么吗
You know what that is?
那就是爱
That's love.
也有可能是
And possibly
酒精混合了强效抗生素的效果
alcohol mixed with some very powerful antibiotics.
巴尼也是那样看你的
And that's how Barney sees you.
我还知道你看巴尼 也是如此
And I know that's how you see Barney.
我想引用泰德的梦境日志
I'd like to start the service
作为开场白
with a passage from Ted's dream journal.
像溺水时
"Drowning.
稀薄空气
"Gasping for air.
无法逃离
No escape."
等下 那是说越南的吗
Wait, is that about Vietnam?
是说健康食品超市的
It's about Whole Foods.
巴尼
Barney.
我们俩不会结婚的
We are not getting married.
而且这个走廊也太窄了
And those aisles are too narrow!
但是你俩必须得结婚 否则
But you two have to get married-- otherwise, it's just
那只是一场毫无价值和意义的 令人作恶的一夜情
a cheap, meaningless, disgusting one-night stand.
等下 咱们得搞清楚 你刚才用
Wait, just to be clear, you're saying you're opposed
"毫无价值和意义 令人作恶"来形容一夜情
to cheap, meaningless, disgusting one-night stands?
对啊
Yes.
巴尼 你没看出来吗
Barney... don't you see?
你的瘾戒掉了
Your detox is done!
你已经不再执念于一夜情了
You're over one-night stands!
苍天啊 你说的太对了
Oh, my God, you're right!
我自由了
I'm free!
是啊 所以如果你能再考虑一下 就一小下
Yeah. So if you think about it-- but not too much--
我和卡莉搞一搞 其实挺好的 对吧
it's actually good that Carly and I hooked up.
对啊 是不错
Yeah, it's really good.
从功夫上看 好像他还是五十岁一样
I mean, this guy goes at it like he's still in his 50s.
嘿 来根雪茄 你个疯丫头
Hey, have a cigar, you big crazy!
喂 别以为这事儿就这么完了
Hey, don't try to make this okay.
你还睡着我妹妹呢
You still slept with my sister.
跟我保证 你永永远远也不再睡了
Promise me you will never, ever do that again.
我保证
I promise.
你刚才眨眼了
You just winked.
我没有啊
No, I didn't.
-你又眨了  -就是没有
-You did it again! -No, I didn't!
你发誓 行吗
You swear, right?
当然可以了
Yeah. Of course.
那天晚上
That night,
虽然罗宾还是买不到啤酒
even though she still couldn't get a beer,
但她感受到了来自戒指的真正能量
Robin realized the true power of the ring.
Drew Holcomb and The Neighbors - What Would I Do Without You
嘿 罗宾
Hey, Robin.
有没有想到你订婚后
Did you ever figure out how you're gonna get
怎么才能买到喝的
a drink at the bar now that you're engaged?
嗯 当然 我知道以后都要怎么做了
Oh, sure. I know a way that's gonna last forever.
加冰威士忌
Scotch on the rocks?
马上就来
Coming right up.
在你们对这帽子发表评论之前
Now, before you say anything about the hat...
我得说 这个新女孩有个完美的翘臀
this new girl's ass is phenomenal!
嘿 马修 来看看这个
Hey, Marshall, you got to see this.
他们肯定把我下的单登记错了
The catalog must have mixed up my order.
你绝对想不到这牛仔裤是什么样子
You won't believe the jeans they just sent me.
超级搞笑 是不
Hilarious, right?
是啊
Totally.
你看起来就像一位 开着装满过期麦圈和空饮料瓶
You look like some suburban mom who drives a minivan
小货卡的郊区母亲
filled with stale Cheerios and empty juice boxes...
有可能做辣肉酱通心粉和炸玉米派当晚餐
probably makes chili mac and Frito pie for dinner...
闻起来有种薄荷香烟的味道
smells like that menthol cigarette that she snuck while
仿佛在等待 迎接他那练曲棍球的孩儿回家
she was waiting to pick her kids up from hockey practice.
快给我过来
Get over here!
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看